Guide to the Jane Conlon Muller Oral History Collection AIA.012
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Charles J. Hynes (1935 - ), 1991; 1 cassette, 1 master compact disc, 1 access compact disc
  - Charles J. Hynes - 2 December 1991, Dec 2, 1991; cuid690; [00:00 - 10:00] Kings county district attorney Background - family, childhood, where he developed his Irish identity. How he became involved in Irish American activities - protesting hunger strikes, co-founding Irish Solidarity Day.; 1 ma
    [16:38] Do you feel that the Irish have been tagged incorrectly as drunks? What do you think is the reason that they've been so tagged?